Guide to the Britton and Rey, Lithographers. Artotypes: Artistic homes of California [chiefly San Francisco], published in San Francisco Newsletter and Advertiser, 1887-1902
Department of Special Collections
- Series 2. New Series
  - Artistic Homes of California - Residence of J.J. Rauer, North side of Ellis, between Gough & Octavia Sts., San FranciscoAug. 16, 1890., No. 60 (Folder 10)
  - Artistic Homes of California - Residence of William E. Dargie, 1168 Jackson St., Oakland.Aug. 30, 1890., No. 62 (Folder 10)
  - Artistic Homes of California at San Rafael - Residences of Mr. John F. Boyd, Mr. L.H. Sweeney, Mr. Louis B. Parrott, and Mr. A.W. Foster.Sept. 6, 1890., No. 63 (Folder 10)
  - Artistic Homes of California at San Rafael - Residences of Mr. William Babcock, Mr. William Lichtenberg, Mr. Sidney V. Smith, and Mr. M.H. deYoung.Sept. 13, 1890., No. 64 (Folder 10)
  - Business Blocks of San Francisco - Mariposa Block, SE corner: Divisadero & Fell Sts.Sept. 20, 1890., No. 65 (Folder 10)
  - Artistic Homes of California - Residence of Mr. F.A. Hyde, 2012 Pacific Ave., between Laguna & Octavia Sts., San FranciscoSept. 27, 1890., No. 66 (Folder 10)
  - The California Hotel and Theatre, Bush St., between Kearny & Grant Aves., San FranciscoOct. 4, 1890., No. 67 (Folder 10)
  - Artistic Homes of California - Residences of James Hogg, James U. Hastings, W.B. Wilshire, and Albert Seiz, 2614-16-18-20 Buchanan St., between Pacific Ave. & Broadway St., San FranciscoOct. 11, 1890., No. 68 (Folder 10)
  - James Lick Free Baths, Tenth St. near Howard, San FranciscoNov. 8, 1890., No. 73 (Folder 10)
  - Artistic Homes of California - Residence of William Fries, 1814 Washington St., San FranciscoNov. 15, 1890., No. 74 (Folder 10)
  - "Aux Ville de France", Maison Truffert-Robes et Trousseau, 609 Taylor St., San FranciscoNov. 22, 1890., No. 75 (Folder 10)
  - Artistic Homes of California - Residence of Mr. Louis Glass, Jones St. between Washington & Jackson, San FranciscoNov. 29, 1890., No. 76 (Folder 10)
  - Artistic Homes of California - Residences of Chas. F. and Frank P. Doe, NE corner: Laguna & California Sts, San FranciscoJan. 3, 1891., No. 78 (Folder 10)
  - Artistic Homes of California - Swell Apartments, A.S. Baldwin's New Building, 1415-1417 Van Ness Ave., near Pine, San FranciscoJan. 10, 1891., No. 79 (Folder 10)
  - Artistic Homes of California - View of North side Pacific Ave., between Pierce & Scott Sts., San FranciscoJan. 17, 1891., No. 80 (Folder 10)
  - Artistic Homes of California - Residence of Robert Dickson, NW corner: Haight & Baker Sts., San FranciscoJan. 31, 1891., No. 81 (Folder 10)
  - Artistic Homes of California - Residence of J.H. Neustadter, NW corner: Van Ness Ave. & Sacramento St., San FranciscoFeb. 7, 1891., No. 82 (Folder 10)
  - Business Blocks of San Francisco - California Academy of Sciences Building, Market St., between 4th & 5th Sts.Feb. 21, 1891., No. 88 [83?] (Folder 10)
  - Bird's-Eye View of San Francisco - from the Tower of New Chronicle Building, on Kearny & Market Sts., looking North along Kearny, The California Hotel in center.Feb. 28, 1891., No. 84 (Folder 10)
  - Senator George Hearst - Died in Washington, D.C. Feb. 28, 1891, aged 70 years.March 14, 1891., No. 86 (Folder 10)
  - Bird's-Eye View of San Francisco (No.2) - from the Tower of New Chronicle Building looking Northwest.March 21, 1891., No. 87 (Folder 10)
  - Hotel Mirabeau, SE corner: Ellis & Leavenworth Sts., San FranciscoApril 4, 1891., No. 83[88?] (Folder 10)
  - Temple Emau-el - Jewish Synagogue, North side Sutter St., between Stockton and Powell Sts, San FranciscoApril 11, 1891., No. 84 [89?] (Folder 10)
  - Business Blocks of San Francisco - The Nightingale Building, Junction of Market, Van Ness Ave., and Oak St.April 18, 1891., No. 90 (Folder 10)
  - . Business Blocks of San Francisco - Supreme Court Building, NW corner: McCallister & Larkin Sts.April 25, 1891., No. 91 (Folder 10)
  - St. Mary's Cathedral - NW corner: Van Ness Ave. & O'Farrell Sts., San FranciscoMay 2, 1891., No. 92 (Folder 10)
  - Artistic Homes of California - Residence of A.N. Towne, SW corner: California & Jones Sts., San FranciscoMay 9, 1891., No. 93 (Folder 10)
  - First Untiarian Church - SW corner: Geary & Franklin Sts, San FranciscoMay 16, 1891., No. 94 (Folder 10)
  - First Presbyterian Church - SE corner: Sacramento St. & Van Ness Ave., San FranciscoMay 23, 1891., No. 95 (Folder 10)
  - Looking Across Union Square from Geary St., San FranciscoMay 30, 1891., No. 96 (Folder 10)
  - Bird's-Eye View of San Francisco - (No. 3) from Chronicle Tower looking West, Cavalry Church & Poposed Post Office Site in Center.June 6, 1891., No. 97 (Folder 10)
  - Peralta Hall - A School for Girls, Berkeley.June 13, 1891., No. 98 (Folder 10)
  - Artistic Homes of California - Residence of Mayor J.L. Rathbone, NE corner: California & Octavia Sts., San FranciscoJune 20, 1891., No. 99 (Folder 10)
  - Artistic Homes of California - double-sized Residence of Mr. S. Wenban, SE corner: Van Ness Ave. & Jackson Sts., San FranciscoJune 27, 1891., No. 100 (Folder 10)
    1. Dining Room, 2. Conservatory, 3. Billiard Room, 4. Hall, 5. Front Elevation, 6. Front Parlor.
  - Bird's-Eye Views of San Francisco - No. 7, from new City Hall, looking North along Hyde St., No. 101, July 4, 1891. (Folder 10)
  - Bird's-Eye Views of San Francisco - No. 8, from Russian Hill, looking Northeast., No. 102, July 11, 1891. (Folder 10)
  - Bird's-Eye Views of San Francisco - No. 9, from Sutter St., looking North on Powell, showing California St. Hill & residences of Mrs. J.C. Flood, Mrs. Hopkins-Searls, & Hon. Leland Stanford., No. 103, July 18, 1891. (Folder 10)
  - Bird's-Eye Views of San Francisco - No. 10, North Point & Sea Wall from Telegraph Hill.Aug. 1, 1891., No. 105 (Folder 10)
  - The Colonial, SE corner: Pine & Jones Sts., San FranciscoAug. 8, 1891., No. 106 (Folder 10)
  - Business Blocks of San Francisco - The Donohoe Building, NE corner: Market & Taylor Sts.Aug. 15, 1891., No. 107 (Folder 10)
  - Bird's-Eye Views of San Francisco - No. 11, from Market & 7th Sts., looking Northeast, Murphy Building and J.J. O'Brien & Co. in foreground.Aug. 29, 1891., No. 109 (Folder 10)
  - Bird's-Eye Views of San Francisco - No. 8, Van Ness Ave. from Geary St., looking North, Concordia Club on right.Sept. 12, 1891., No. 111 (Folder 10)
  - New Clay St. Flat, South side Clay St., between Leavenworth & Hyde St., San FranciscoOct. 24, 1891., No. 115 (Folder 10)
  - Artistic Homes of California - East side of Lyon, between Oak & Page Sts., San FranciscoNov. 14, 1891., No. 117 (Folder 10)
  - Artistic Homes of California - Residence of Henry T. Scott, SW corner: Clay & Laguna Sts., San FranciscoDec. 5, 1891., No. 118 (Folder 10)
  - April 8, 1893. Artistic Homes of California - "The Seattle" house & flats, SW corner: Golden Gate Ave. & Steiner St., San Francisco, No. 145 (Folder 10)
  - Business Blocks of San Francisco - The MacDonough Building & Theatre, corner: Broadway & 14th Sts., San FranciscoApril 15, 1893., No. 146 (Folder 10)
- Series 3. Miscellaneous
  - High School, San Jose, Cal.Nov. 5, 1887. (Folder 20)
  - Safe Deposit Block, San Jose, Cal.Nov. 19, 1887. (Folder 20)
  - Christmas Number, 1887. (double-sized, printed in pamphlet format) I.O.O.F. Building, SW corner: Market & 7th Sts., and Union Club Buiding, NW corner: Post & Stockton Sts. (on reverse), S.F.1887 Dec. (Folder 20)
  - Christmas Number, 1887. (quadruple-sized) San Rafael and its Environs 1887 Dec. (Folder 20)
    1. Residence of Hall McAllister, 2. Avenue in Coleman Tract, 3. Residence of William Lichtenberg, 4. Grounds of William Babcock, 5. Residence of William Babcock, 6. Depot S.F. & N.P.R.R. Co., 7. Residence of Sydney V. Smith, 8. Residence of A.W. Foster, 9. Residence of Mrs. Alex Forbes, 10. Residence of William T. Coleman, 11. Residence of Mrs. C.V. Johnston, 12. Hotel Rafael, 13. Residence of John F. Boyd, 14. Residence of Albert Dibblee, 15. Residence of George Wilson, 16. Profile Island, 17. Residence of Louis Sloss, 18. Corner in Vineyard, 19. Conservatory in grounds of William T. Coleman, 20. Grounds of A.E. Kent, 21. Hotel Rafael grounds, 22. Marinita Park, 23. Flowers in December, grounds of William Babcock, 24. Terrace in grounds of William T. Coleman, 25. San Rafael with Mount Tamalpais in the distance.
  - St. James Hotel, San Jose.April 4, 1888. (Folder 21)
  - Christmas Number, 1888. Views in Golden Gate Park and Vicinity - Hayes St. entrance, Near the Lodge, Conservatory Valley, from the Conservatory looking south, Deer Park, Bridle Path, Sharon Memorial & children's playground, Stanyan St. entrance, Interior of Conservatory, Francis Scott Key Monument, Band Stand, Pond near Haight St. entrance, Rustic Grotto, Halleck Monument, Seal Rocks & Cliff House.1888 Dec. (Folder 21)
  - Encampment of Second Brigade, N.G.C. --- Camp Waterman, Santa Cruz, Week Ending Aug. 23, 1890. (double-sized) 1890 Aug. 23 (Folder 21)
    Images as follows: Company Street, Brigade Headquarters, Consolidated Bands, Brigade Dress Parade, Battery Firing, Guards' Camp-fire.
  - Christmas Number, 1890. Panoramic View of San Francisco - from California & Powell Sts., looking towards the Bay. (triple-sized)1890 Dec. (Folder 21)
  - Lemon Curer and Warehouse - for Crocker & Co., at the Las Fuentes Rancho, Montecito. (drawing)Oct. 17, 1891. (Folder 22)
  - Religious Edifices, Erected 1891 - St. John's Episcopal Church, Congregation Beth Israel, 1st New Jerusalem Church (Swedenborgian), Greek Church.Jan. 9, 1892. (Folder 22)
  - (double-sided) View of Alcatraz Island, San Francisco Bay, and Park Lodge, Golden Gate Park.July 10, 1897. (Folder 22)
  - (double-sided) View of new Cliff House and Baths from Sutro Heights, and Huntington Falls, Golden Gate Park.July 10, 1897. (Folder 22)
  - Temple Emanuel - Sutter St., San Francisco.July 29, 1899. (Folder 22)
  - Residence of Henry J. Crocker, Laguna & Washington Sts., S.F.Aug. 19, 1899.
  - New Law Courts.Aug. 26, 1899. (Folder 22)
  - Artistic Homes of California - Residence of William J. Gunn, NE corner: Devisadero & Green Sts., S.F.Sept. 23, 1899. (Folder 22)
  - Artistic Homes of California - Residence of William F. Herrin, NE corner: Broadway & Scott Sts., S.F.Sept. 30, 1899. (Folder 22)
  - Artistic Homes of California - NW corner: Jackson & Pierce Sts., S.F.Sept. 30, 1899. (Folder 22)
  - Artistic Homes of California - Residence of Dr. Robert A. McLean, corner: Pacific Ave. & Devisadero Sts., S.F.Oct. 14, 1899. (Folder 22)
  - Artistic Homes of California - Residence of Hon. James D. Phelan, 17th & Valencia Sts., S.F.Oct. 21, 1899. (Folder 22)
  - Artistic Homes of California - Residence of Mr. Julian Sontag, NE corner: Vallejo & Scott Sts., S.F.Oct. 28, 1899. (Folder 22)
  - Artistic Homes of California - Residence of George D. Lucy, SW corner: Fulton & Scott Sts., S.F.Nov. 11, 1899. (Folder 22)
  - Artistic Homes of California - Residence of E.G. Schonwasser, 2420 Van Ness Ave., S.F.Nov. 18, 1899. (Folder 22)
  - Business Blocks of San Francisco - Caroline Building, 52 First St.March 24, 1900. (Folder 23)
  - Accepted Design for the Mutual Savings Bank's new Building, Market St., San Francisco.April 28, 1900. (Folder 23)
  - Artistic Homes of California - San Francisco,Nov. 17, 1900. (Folder 23)
    1. Hall Residence of Samuel N. Napalthy, 2404 Broadway. -- 2. Residence of Samuel N. Napalthy, 2404 Broadway. -- 3. Residence of Sydney M. Smith, Webster & Broadway. -- 4. Residence of E. Avery McCarthy, 2400 Broadway, corner Steiner.
  - Beautiful Belvedere (double-sized) - J.D. Maxwell, Church, Belvedere Land Co. Cottages, School, W.M. Willett, Chester H. Evans, Wm. P. Harrison, F.W. Boyle, Fred. Greenwood, Dr. B.M. Haines, Jas. S. Hawkin's launch, H.C. Tilden, Capt. H.S. Thompson, C.S. Holmes, Dr. Haines, Corinthian Yacht Club.Sept. 14, 1901. (Folder 23)
  - Artistic Homes of Alameda (double-sized) - Jas. A. Waymire, Geo. A. Moore, C. Bryant, Dr. W.R. Cluness, Dr. Alfred Sander, Wm. F. Barton, Geo. H. Tyson, R.H. Rosseter, Dr. Chas. W.R. von Radesky, F.W. Voogt, Chas. C. Hanley, W.M. Rank, Dr. A.A. Stafford, H.C. Havens.Sept. 28, 1901. (Folder 23)
  - Mrs. Chas. C. Moore in her locomobile touring car, at San Mateo.Aug. 2, 1902. (Folder 23)
  - Artistic Homes of California - Residence of Isaac Trumbo, SE corner: Sutter & Octavia Sts., S.F.ca. 1902 (Folder 23)
    1. Reception Room, 2. Hall, 3. Drawing Room, 4. Drawing Room, 5. Corner Elevation, 6. Dining Room.
  - Artistic Homes of California - Residence of Mrs. A.R. Baldwin, NW corner: Devisadero & Union Sts., S.F.ca. 1902 (Folder 23)
- Series 4. Panoramic Series
  - Picturesque San Francisco - View from California & Mason Sts., looking Northwest, showing Crocker, Huntington, & Flood Mansions; and No. 17, June 13, 1896. Picturesque San Francisco - Powell St., from Sutter St., looking North.Feb. 22, 1896., No. 1 (Folder 24)
  - Picturesque San Francisco - View from California & Mason Sts., looking towards Telegraph Hill; and Shoshone Tunnel, Cañon of Grand River.Feb. 29, 1896., No. 2. (Folder 24)
  - Picturesque San Francisco - View from Broadway & Divisadero Sts., looking Northeast, showing Alcatraz & Angel Islands; and No. 15, May 30, 1896. Picturesque San Francisco - View from Russian Hill, looking Northeast, Goat Island in the distance.March 7, 1896., No. 3 (Folder 24)
  - Picturesque San Francisco - View from Lafayette Park, Clay & Octavia Sts., looking Souteast; and 40th Anniversary Number, July 18, 1896. Evidently Humorous - from original painting in Munich Academy of Art by Th. Cedertrom.March 14, 1896., No. 4 (Folder 24)
  - Picturesque San Francisco - View from Hopkins Art Building, looking East; and 40th Anniversary Number, July 18, 1896. Death of the Bedouin - from original painting by C. Rud Huber.March 21, 1896., No. 5 (Folder 24)
  - Picturesque San Francisco - View from Harrison & Essex Sts., looking North, showing Palace Hotel ...; and 40th Anniversary Number, July 18, 1896. Fishermen on Lake Como, Italy.April 4, 1896., No. 7 (Folder 24)
  - Picturesque San Francisco - View of Alcatraz Island; and 40th Anniversary Number, July 18, 1896. The Lost Dinner - from original painting by Ed. Borchard.April 11, 1896., No. 8 (Folder 24)
  - Picturesque San Francisco - View from Hopkins Art Association, looking North, showing San Francisco Bay and Alcatraz Island; and No. 12, May 9, 1896. Picturesque San Francisco - looking out the Golden Gate.April 18, 1896., No. 9 (Folder 24)
  - Picturesque San Francisco - View from Hopkins Art Association, looking South; and No. 20, July 4, 1896. Picturesque San Francisco - The Alameda, Garden & Music Stand, Presidio.April 25, 1896., No. 10 (Folder 24)
  - Picturesque San Francisco - View from Broadway & Devisadero Sts., looking Northeast; and No. 21. July 11, 1896. Picturesque San Francisco - View of Point Bonita from near Land's End Station.May 2, 1896., No. 11 (Folder 24)
  - Picturesque San Francisco- Baker's Beach and Fort Point.May 16, 1896., No. 13 (Folder 24)
  - Picturesque San Francisco- Baker's Beach and Fort Point.May 23, 1896., No. 14 (Folder 24)
  - Picturesque San Francisco - Looking down the Ocean Beach from the Cliff House, showing pier of Lurline Baths.June 20, 1896., No. 18 (Folder 25)
  - Picturesque San Francisco - View of Presidio, from Upper Road looking East.June 27, 1896., No. 19 (Folder 25)
  - Picturesque San Francisco - View of California St. from Montgomery, looking West.July 18, 1896., No. 22 (Folder 25)
  - Picturesque San Francisco - View of Market St. from Grant Ave., looking towards the Ferries.July 25, 1896., No. 23 (Folder 25)
  - Picturesque San Francisco - View of San Francisco and Bay from Alcatraz Island.Aug. 22, 1896., No. 26 (Folder 25)
  - Picturesque San Francisco - North side of Market St., from Powell, looking East.Sept. 12, 1896., No. 29 (Folder 25)
  - Picturesque San Francisco - Views in Golden Gate Park.Oct. 4, 1896., No. 31 (Folder 25)
  - Picturesque San Francisco - Deer Paddock, Golden Gate Park.Nov. 7, 1896., No. 37 (Folder 25)
  - Picturesque San Francisco - View from dome of City Hall, looking Northeast, Nob Hill in background.Nov. 28, 1896., No. 40 (Folder 25)
  - Picturesque San Francisco - View from dome of City Hall, looking North, showing Hyde & Larkin Sts.Dec. 12, 1896., No. 42 (Folder 25)
  - Picturesque San Francisco - View from dome of City Hall, looking West, up Fulton St., Lone Mountain in distance.Dec. 19, 1896., No. 43 (Folder 25)
  - Picturesque San Francisco - Fort Point, entrance of Golden Gate.Jan. 23, 1897., No. 46 (Folder 26)
  - Picturesque San Francisco - View of San Francisco Bay, from Lime Point.Feb. 6, 1897., No. 48 (Folder 26)
  - Picturesque San Francisco - looking through the Golden Gate, showing Fort & Lime Points.Feb. [13, 1897?]., No. 49 (Folder 26)
  - Picturesque San Francisco - Interior of Conservatory, Golden Gate Park.Feb. 20, 1897., No. 50 (Folder 26)
  - Picturesque San Francisco - Scenes in Chinatown: Interior of Chinese Theatre, showing stage arrangement.March 13, 1897., No. 53 (Folder 26)
  - Picturesque San Francisco - Scenes in Chinatown: Smoking Room, Chinese restaurant.March 20, 1897.., No. 54 (Folder 26)
  - Picturesque San Francisco - Scenes in Chinatown: Dining Room, Chinese restaurant.March 27, 1897.., No. 55 (Folder 26)
  - Picturesque San Francisco - Scenes in Chinatown: Chinese Apothecary.April 3, 1897.., No. 56 (Folder 26)
  - Picturesque San Francisco - Scenes in Chinatown: God in Joss Temple.., No. 57. (Folder 26)
  - Picturesque San Francisco - Scenes in Chinatown: Opium den underground, by flashlight.., No. 58 (Folder 26)
  - Picturesque San Francisco - a carved Chinese bedroom set, property of Mrs. Jane Stanford.May 1, 1897., No. 59 (Folder 26)
  - Picturesque San Francisco - Relics of Old Iron Buildings, Jackson St., in rear of post office, shipped around Cape Horn in the early days of San Francisco.May 8, 1897., No. 60 (Folder 26)
  - Picturesque San Francisco - Bay of San Francisco, showing Goat Island, from Harrison & Essex Sts.May 15, 1897., No. 61 (Folder 26)
  - Picturesque San Francisco - View of Golden Gate, Fort Point, Harbor View, and Gas Company's Works.May 22, 1897., No. 62 (Folder 26)
  - Picturesque San Francisco - The Cyclists' Rendezvous, Boat House on Stow Lake.[May 29, 1897?]., No. 63 (Folder 26)
  - Picturesque California - Yosemite Valley, showing the Three Brothers and the Merced River.June 5, 1897., No. 64 (Folder 27)
  - Picturesque California - Views on the Mount Tamalpais scenic railway.June 12, 1897., No. 65 (Folder 27)
  - Picturesque California - Yosemite Valley, Glacier Point (3300 ft. hight) and South Dome.June 19, 1897., No. 66 (Folder 27)
  - Picturesque California - Yosemite Valley, sunrise in Mirror Lake.June 26, 1897., No. 67 (Folder 27)
  - Picturesque California - Yosemite Valley, view from Franklin Rock, showing Vernal Falls (336 ft. high).July 3, 1897., No. 68 (Folder 27)
  - Picturesque California - Views on the Mount Tamalpais scenic railway.July 17, 1897., No. 69 (Folder 27)
  - Picturesque California - Yosemite Valley, Upper & Lower Yosemite Falls.July 24, 1897., No. 70 (Folder 27)
  - Picturesque California - Around the Bay: Alcatraz, Oakland, Lake Merritt, Sausalito, Mare Island.July 31, 1897., No. 71 (Folder 27)
  - Picturesque California - Across the Golden Gate, looking over the fort; and Seal Rock, after a storm.Aug. 7, 1897., No. 72 (Folder 27)
  - Picturesque San Francisco - Views in Golden Gate Park: colonial kitchen in art museum; and new bridge & driveway.Aug. 21, 1897., No. 74 (Folder 27)
  - Picturesque San Francisco - Monuments in Golden Gate Park: Francis Scott Key, General U.S. Grant, Starr King.Sept. 11, 1897., No. 76 (Folder 27)
  - Picturesque San Francisco - Admission Day Fountain, dedicated to the N.S.G.W. by Mayor James D. Phelan, 1897.Sept. 18, 1897., No. 77 (Folder 27)
  - Picturesque San Francisco - View of North Beach from San Francisco Bay.Sept. 25, 1897., No. 78 (Folder 27)
  - Picturesque San Francisco - View of Alcatraz Island & Tiburon from corner of Hyde & Lombard Sts.Oct. 2, 1897., No. 79 (Folder 27)
  - Picturesque San Francisco - Bird's-eye view from corner: Lombard & Hyde Sts., looking East.Oct. 9, 1897., No. 80 (Folder 27)
  - Picturesque San Francisco - On the Seal Rocks.Oct. 16, 1897., No. 81 (Folder 27)
  - Picturesque San Francisco - New Stevenson Monument in Portsmouth Square, Washington & Kearny Sts.Oct. 23, 1897., No. 82 (Folder 28)
  - Business Blocks of San Francisco - Spring Valley Water Works Building, SE corner: Geary & Stockton Sts.Nov. 6, 1897., No. 84 (Folder 28)
  - Picturesque San Francisco - Scenes in Chinatown.Nov. 20, 1897., No. 86 (Folder 28)
  - Picturesque California - Old Adobe House.Nov. 27, 1897., No. 87 (Folder 28)
  - Wildflowers of California.Dec. 4, 1897., No. 88 (Folder 28)
  - Artistic Homes of California - (double-sized) Residence of Sir Claus Spreckels, corner: Van Ness Ave. & Clay St., S.F.Jan. 1, 1898., No. __ [90?] (Folder 28)
  - Picturesque San Francisco - Union Square from Post & Powell Sts., showing Chronicle Tower, Call Building, City of Paris, Spring Valley Water Works Building.Jan. 8, 1898., No. 91 (Folder 28)
  - Picturesque San Francisco - View of San Francisco from Park Hill, looking East.Jan. 15, 1898., No. 92 (Folder 28)
  - Business Blocks of San Francisco - (double-sized) Claus Spreckels Building, corner: Market & Third Sts.Jan. 29, 1897., No. __ [93?] (Folder 28)
  - Picturesque California - Public Highway, San Mateo County.Feb. 5, 1898., No. 94 (Folder 28)
  - Business Blocks of San Francisco - New Office Building, SE corner: Sutter & Montgomery Sts., erected by George Whittell.Feb. 12, 1898., No. 95 (Folder 28)
  - Picturesque California - Scenes on the line of S.F. & N.P.R.R., near Ukiah: the "Narrows" at Blue Lakes, Loading Tan Bark.Feb. 19, 1898., No. 96 (Folder 28)
  - Picturesque California - Views of Mare Island Navy Yard: Feb. 26, 1898., No. 97 (Folder 28)
    Ordinance yard and steam engineering machine shop, drive in front of Officers' residence, water front with dry dock & construction dept. buildings, and Harbor, Boston, & Thetis ships at wharf with Vallejo across the channel.
  - Picturesque San Francisco - Trinity Episcopal Church, corner: Gough & Bush Sts., showing interior and new memorial windows.March 5, 1898., No. 98 (Folder 28)
  - Picturesque California - Views of Alcatraz Island: from the island looking Northeast, front view of light station, officers' residences, and view of South side of island.March 12, 1898., No. 99 (Folder 28)
  - Picturesque San Francisco - Views of the garden at Fort Mason.March 19, 1898., No. 100 (Folder 28)
  - Picturesque San Francisco - Views in Jefferson Square, between Golden Gate Ave. & Eddy St., Gough & Laguna Sts.March 26, 1898., No. 101 (Folder 28)